According to YouTube statistics, only a
small percentage of people that watch my
videos are actually subscribed. So, if
you end up liking this video, consider
subscribing. It's free and you can
always information is so important. It's
going directly to the president of the
United [music] States. I made a guy cry
once in a meeting. So, he gave me some
information. It was good. It was the
analysts were happy with it. It helped
fill in a couple of gaps. [music] He
thought it was the greatest information
that's ever been passed to the American
government. So, I said, "Listen," I go,
"Buddy, your information went directly
to the president of the [music] United
States." He said, "You're kidding me." I
said, "No, directly to the president." I
said, "I wrote the report. I [music]
sent it to the White House." He looked
at the report. What did he say? I said,
"The president read the report and he
said, "You're kidding me." It goes like
this. Oh my. [music] So, I I write this
up. I said, "Oh, I told him the
president." My boss says, "You want to
have some fun?" He goes, [music] "Dummy
up a uh an award certificate. Put the
CIA seal on it." So, I said, "Oh, that
would be fun." So, I did a I did a in in
just in Word, [music] you know, and clip
art. So, I did this, you know, Central
Intelligence Agency, United States of
America. Had the guy's name, a
certificate of whatever. You put the CIA
seal on it, and then I just forged the
[music] director's name because how's he
going to know what the director's
signature looks like? So, I go to the
meeting the next month, and I said, I
told you [music] last month that your
information went directly to the
president of the United States. He said,
"Yes." Said, "I have [music] something
for you from the director of the Central
Intelligence Agency." And I give him
this phony certificate. He looks at it
and he bursts into [music] tears. And I
said, "Congratulations, my friend."
[laughter] I said, "But listen, you
know, I have to take this back and keep
it in the safe [music] because you can't
be seen with this. You'll be killed." He
goes, "Of course. Of course." I can't
believe it. Oh my god. [music] I had him
hooked. He was ready to name his kids
after me. That's how successful it was.
But you just play on their egos and
[music] they eat it up. They eat it up
cuz they're all narcissists anyway. Not
all, but you know, most of them are
narcissists. They need to be stroked.
>> I don't I don't see how you think I owe
the government.
>> I'm not saying you owe the government
anything. I'm just saying that the
ideals that you had, you must have had
in 2084,
1889.
>> 89. Yeah.
>> You must have compromised on those
ideals. You must have at some point.
>> I'm a patriot.
>> Isn't Isn't questioning the government
and holding the government accountable
something that the United States was
founded on?
>> I don't know the answer to that.
>> Of course, it is.
>> How How isn't that in the Constitution?
>> I I don't know the answer to that
either. Is there can somebody flag where
there's any mention of individual
accountability to the government?
>> The problem is year after year after
year going back to the 1950s the
Pentagon will come in and say we want x
amount of money and Congress says we'll
give you that amount and we'll give you
another 15%. And the Pentagon says
that's great. [music] We don't know what
we'll spend it on because [laughter] we
don't need it but we'll take it. Is it
any wonder that the Pentagon has failed
seven consecutive audits to the point
where the most important auditing firm
in the world, Price Waterhouse Coopers,
gave up in the middle of the last audit
and said [music] it can't be done? That
fully half of the Pentagon's hardware
can't be located, [music] can't be
accounted for. If that's not the
definition of corruption, I don't know
what is.
>> Yeah. And I have a question. [music]
Where is
>> Jeez, what's the worst thing I saw in
prison?
There's no there's not one easy answer
to that. I'm [music] going to give you a
couple.
>> There was this old man who lived in my
housing unit. He was 82 years old.
>> He's probably dead by now.
And [music]
um
>> I was like, "What in the world is this
old man?" A guy was hunched over and he
had a problem where he was constantly
[__] [music] himself
and he would you he could feel it coming
and he would get [music] up and then it
would run down his pant leg and it would
make this trail of diarrhea from his
cell to the to the uh bathroom. [music]
And I tell you, there was this this
young African-American kid, I say young,
he was 18 years old on a drug charge in
the same cell. He used to beat [music]
the [__] out of this old man
>> because his body was so broken down that
he couldn't get on his hands and knees
and clean up his own [__] So he asked
me one time, he lived about [music] five
cells down for me. He asked me one time
if I would talk to the blackshot caller
and ask cuz I had good [music] relations
with everybody. I was like a oneman
United Nations in there. Would I talk to
the blackshot caller and ask the
blackshot caller to tell this kid to
stop beating him up? And I said, "Well,
let me let me poke around and see what I
can what I can do." Well, the first
thing I did is I went to the law library
to look this guy up and see what his
crime was. And his crime was this. When
he was 80 years old,
>> he arranged to purchase a 9-year-old
girl from her drugaddicted mother in
Atlanta, Georgia. This guy lived in
Chicago. And he drove at the age of 80.
He drove from Chicago to Atlanta
>> to human traffic this 9-year-old girl so
that he could rape her whenever he
wanted to.
It turned out there was no 9-year-old
girl and there was no drug addicted
mother. It was just an FBI agent.
>> And so they grabbed him as soon as he
arrived at the hotel where the purchase
was supposed to take place. And he got
17 years in prison. Now he was Barack
Obama used a drone to murder Anoir
Alaki.
>> Yep.
>> And whether you like the man's politics
or not, he was an American citizen who
had never been charged with a crime. And
then a week later, Obama droned his
16-year-old son and 14-year-old nephew
who were sitting in a coffee shop having
a cup of tea. Also, American citizens
who had never been charged with a crime
and they were children. So, yeah, the
CIA does all kinds of things like that.
>> What about domestically? Well, you know,
I keep thinking back to Eric Holder's
testimony before the uh the Senate Armed
Services Committee when Rand Paul asked
him, "Does the president have the legal
authority to murder an American on US
soil?" Well, Senator, you know, just
answer the question. It's a yes or no
question. Yes, he has the authority.
Now, has he done that? We didn't know.
But the attorney general of the United
States said that the president can
murder an American citizen in the United
States if the president believes that he
presents a clear and present danger to
the national security. That's sick.
Every single day
>> you think that Chinese students are in
America spying on behalf of China?
>> Yes.
>> How could you be so sure?
>> I'm 1,000% sure.
>> How could you be so sure? because we
frequently arrest them and then trade
them for Americans who are in Chinese
prisons.
[clears throat]
>> Yeah.
>> And they're masquerading as students.
>> Mhm. PhD candidates always in the hard
sciences. Always.
>> So, China are the long-term adversary.
And what is it that China China want?
What is it they're doing?
>> And what is the outcome?
>> I think they want a couple of things. I
think that
on a more immediate basis they want
reunification with Taiwan. It's going to
happen someday. Even the Taiwanese will
tell you, "Yes, we're a part of China,
but we're kind of not a part of China.
We're not really independent, but we are
kind of independent." And even American
policy is that Taiwan is a part of
China.
We can't afford it. Our interest on the
national debt is now the third largest
expenditure in government between the
Pentagon and social security and then
the the interest on the debt.
>> And why does this bother you?
>> Because we're going bankrupt and all the
while the China the Chinese are letting
us spend ourselves into oblivion. The
Chinese don't spend that kind of money.
How come I can't have a bullet train
that goes 400 m an hour? How come I
can't get to Chicago in 3 hours by
train? You know, how come the airports
in my country look like [__] and you go
to Chinese airports and they're pristine
with like the most amazing services and
the best restaurants? How come Chinese
roads don't have potholes? And in my
town, it's like driving across Bosnia.
It's because they decided not to spend
their money on weapons. They spend it on
infrastructure.
I got a call from a Japanese diplomat
and he said, "Hey, let's have lunch." I
said, "Great." So, we meet at a
restaurant on Capitol Hill. His English
was so bad that we had to do the lunches
in Arabic. We talked about the the
Israeli election, the Turkish election.
We talked about the peace process. And
at the end of it, he said to me, "So,
what's next for you?" And I said, "I
think I'm going to resign soon." And he
says, "No, don't do that. if you give me
information, I can give you money. And I
said, "What in the world is wrong with
you? Shame on you for cold pitching me."
And I indignantly got up and walked out.
And I went directly without stopping to
the office of the Senate Security
Officer. And I said, "I was just pitched
by a foreign intelligence officer. I
need to report it." He said, "Was it
that damn Russian again?" And I said,
"No, it was Japanese." So he said, "Sit
at this standalone computer, write it
up, and I'll send it to the FBI." I
said, "Fine." I wrote the entire thing
as a memo. He sent it to the FBI. The
next day, he calls me and says, "Two FBI
agents are going to come up. They want
to interview you." I said, "Great." I go
back down to the security vault and
these two young FBI agents come. I tell
them the story again. And they said,
"Okay, here's what we want you to do. We
want you to call him back and invite him
to lunch and try to get him to tell you
exactly what information he's looking
for and what he's willing to pay for it.
We'll just be at the next table. We'll
listen to everything. The morning of the
lunch, they called me and said,
"Something came up. We can't do it. So,
do the lunch and write another memo."
So, I did and I wrote up a comprehensive
report. I sent it back to the FBI. Then,
they asked me to do it a third time, a
fourth time, and a fifth time, which I
did. And in the final lunch, and in that
final lunch, he says, "I got promoted. I
got my dream job. I'm going to be the
number two at the Japanese embassy in
Cairo." I said, "Congratulations." I
shook his hand. I never talked to him
again. A year later, I've been arrested.
And we get discovery. And we see that
there never was any Japanese diplomat.
He was just an an Asian FBI agent who
didn't speak a word of Japanese, but he
did speak Arabic. He pretended to not
speak English. Heat. Heat. [music]
[music]